<Namespace Name="Android.Drm">
  <Docs>
    <summary>Provides classes for managing DRM content and determining the capabilities of DRM plugins
(agents).</summary>
    <remarks><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">Provides classes for managing DRM content and determining the capabilities of DRM plugins
(agents). Common uses of the DRM API include:<list type="bullet"><item><term>Determining which DRM plug-ins (agents) are installed on a device.</term></item><item><term>Retrieving information about specific plug-ins, such as the MIME types and file suffixes
  they support.</term></item><item><term>Registering a user or a device with an online DRM service.</term></item><item><term>Retrieving license constraints for rights-protected content.</term></item><item><term>Checking whether a user has the proper rights to play or use rights-protected
  content.</term></item><item><term>Associating rights-protected content with its license so you can use the
  <c><see cref="T:Android.Media.MediaPlayer" /></c> API to play the content.</term></item></list><format type="text/html"><h2>DRM Overview</h2></format></para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">The Android platform provides an extensible DRM framework that lets applications manage
rights-protected content according to the license constraints that are associated with the
content. The DRM framework supports many DRM schemes; which DRM schemes a device supports
is up to the device manufacturer.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">The Android DRM framework is implemented in two architectural layers (see figure below):<list type="bullet"><item><term>A DRM framework API, which is exposed to applications through the Android
application framework and runs through the Dalvik VM for standard applications.</term></item><item><term>A native code DRM manager, which implements the DRM framework and exposes an
interface for DRM plug-ins (agents) to handle rights management and decryption for various
DRM schemes.</term></item></list><format type="text/html"><img src="../../../images/drm_arch.png" alt="DRM architecture diagram" border="0" /></format></para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">For application developers, the DRM framework offers an abstract, unified API that
simplifies the management of rights-protected content. The API hides the complexity of DRM
operations and allows a consistent operation mode for both rights-protected and unprotected content
across a variety of DRM schemes. For device manufacturers, content owners, and Internet digital
media providers the DRM framework’s plugin architecture provides a means of adding support for a
specific DRM scheme to the Android system.<format type="text/html"><h2>Using the DRM API</h2></format></para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">In a typical DRM session, an Android application uses the DRM framework API to
instantiate a <c><see cref="T:Android.Drm.DrmManagerClient" /></c>. The application calls various methods
on the DRM client to query rights and perform other DRM-related tasks. Each
<c><see cref="T:Android.Drm.DrmManagerClient" /></c> instance has its own unique ID, so the DRM manager is able to
differentiate callers.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">Although each DRM plug-in may require a different sequence
of API calls, the general call sequence for an application is as follows:<list type="bullet"><item><term>Register the device with an online DRM service.
    </term></item><item><term>Acquire the license that's associated with the rights-protected content.
    </term></item><item><term>Extract constraint information from the license.
    </term></item><item><term>Associate the rights-protected content with its license.
    </term></item></list></para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">You can do this by first using the <c><see cref="M:Android.Drm.DrmManagerClient.AcquireDrmInfo(Android.Drm.DrmInfoRequest)" /></c> method to acquire the registration information, and then using the <c><see cref="M:Android.Drm.DrmManagerClient.ProcessDrmInfo(Android.Drm.DrmInfo)" /></c> method to process the
registration information.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">You can do this by first using the <c><see cref="M:Android.Drm.DrmManagerClient.AcquireDrmInfo(Android.Drm.DrmInfoRequest)" /></c> method to acquire the license information, and then using the <c><see cref="M:Android.Drm.DrmManagerClient.ProcessDrmInfo(Android.Drm.DrmInfo)" /></c> method to process the
license information. You can also use the <c><see cref="M:Android.Drm.DrmManagerClient.AcquireRights(Android.Drm.DrmInfoRequest)" /></c> method.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">You can use the <c><see cref="M:Android.Drm.DrmManagerClient.GetConstraints(Android.Net.Uri, Android.Drm.DrmStoreActionCode)" /></c>
    method to do this.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">You can use the <c><see cref="M:Android.Drm.DrmManagerClient.SaveRights(Android.Drm.DrmRights, System.String, System.String)" /></c> method
    to do this.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">After you make an association between the rights-protected content and its license,
the DRM manager automatically handles rights management for that content. Specifically, the
DRM manager will handle all further licensing checks when you attempt to play the content using
the <c><see cref="T:Android.Media.MediaPlayer" /></c> API.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">To learn how to use the DRM API with a specific DRM plug-in, see the documentation provided
by the plug-in developer.</para></remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>
