<Namespace Name="Android.App">
  <Docs>
    <summary>Contains high-level classes encapsulating the overall Android application model.</summary>
    <remarks><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">Contains high-level classes encapsulating the overall Android application model.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">An Android application is defined using one or more of Android's four core application
components. Two such application components are defined in this package: <c><see cref="T:Android.App.Activity" /></c> and <c><see cref="T:Android.App.Service" /></c>. The other two components are from the <c><see cref="N:Android.Content" /></c> package: <c><see cref="T:Android.Content.BroadcastReceiver" /></c> and <c><see cref="T:Android.Content.ContentProvider" /></c>.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">An <c><see cref="T:Android.App.Activity" /></c> is an application component that provides a screen with which
users can interact in order to do something, such as dial the phone, take a photo, send an email, or
view a map. An activity can start other activities, including activities that live in separate
applications.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">A <c><see cref="T:Android.App.Service" /></c> is an application component that can perform
long-running operations in the background without a user interface. For example, a service
can handle network transactions, play music, or work with a content provider without the user being
aware of the work going on.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">The <c><see cref="T:Android.App.Fragment" /></c> class is also an important part of an application's
design&amp;mdash;especially when designing for large screen devices, such as tablets. A fragment defines
a distinct part of an activity's behavior, including the associated UI. It has its own lifecycle
that is similar to that of the activity and can exist alongside other fragments that are embedded in
the activity. While an activity is running, you can add and remove fragments and include each
fragment in a back stack that's managed by the activity&amp;mdash;allowing the user to navigate
backwards through the fragment states, without leaving the activity.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">This package also defines application utilities, such as dialogs, notifications, and the
action bar.</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">For information about using some the classes in this package, see the following
documents: <format type="text/html"><a href="http://developer.android.com/reference/../guide/topics/fundamentals/activities.html">Activities</a></format>, <format type="text/html"><a href="http://developer.android.com/reference/../guide/topics/fundamentals/services.html">Services</a></format>, <format type="text/html"><a href="http://developer.android.com/reference/../guide/topics/fundamentals/fragments.html">Fragments</a></format>, <format type="text/html"><a href="http://developer.android.com/reference/../guide/topics/ui/actionbar.html">Using the Action Bar</a></format>, <format type="text/html"><a href="http://developer.android.com/reference/../guide/topics/ui/dialogs.html">Creating Dialogs</a></format>, and <format type="text/html"><a href="http://developer.android.com/reference/../guide/topics/ui/notifiers/index.html">Notifying the User</a></format>.</para></remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>
