<Namespace Name="Android.Print">
  <Docs>
    <summary>
Provides classes for implementing print support in applications and also contains all
base classes and abstractions involved in printing.</summary>
    <remarks><format type="text/html"><h3>Overview</h3></format><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">
Provides classes for implementing print support in applications and also contains all
base classes and abstractions involved in printing. These base classes are also used
by other more specialized printing related packages.
</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">
The entry point for interacting with the print system is the <c><see cref="T:Android.Print.PrintManager" /></c>
which is a system service that can be obtained from the current context. The print manager
provides APIs for printing, querying the state of print jobs, etc.
</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc"><format type="text/html"><h3>Print contract</h3></format></para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">
An application that wants to implement printing must extend
<c><see cref="T:Android.Print.PrintDocumentAdapter" /></c> which defines the contract between the system
and the application.The key idea behind this adapter is that the printed content may change
based on the selected print options, such as media size, orientation, which
requires the content to be re-laid out. The constraints according to which the content has
to be laid out are encapsulated in the <c><see cref="T:Android.Print.PrintAttributes" /></c> class. Once
layout is completed the application calls back to the system passing a
<c><see cref="T:Android.Print.PrintDocumentInfo" /></c> instance which describes the generated content. After
the content has been laid out the application may be asked to render some pages of that content
for preview or printing. The range of pages that have to be rendered is abstracted by the
<c><see cref="T:Android.Print.PageRange" /></c> class.
</para><format type="text/html"><h3>Print jobs</h3></format><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">
A print job is represented by the <c><see cref="T:Android.Print.PrintJob" /></c> class which has behavior
methods as well as methods for querying its state. Each print job has a unique id represented
by the <c><see cref="T:Android.Print.PrintJobId" /></c> class and exposes APIs for obtaining a <c><see cref="T:Android.Print.PrintJobInfo" /></c> which is a snapshot of its state. The print job state may
change over time.
</para><format type="text/html"><h3>Printers</h3></format><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc">
An available printer represented by the <c><see cref="T:Android.Print.PrinterInfo" /></c> class has a
unique id which is abstracted by the <c><see cref="T:Android.Print.PrinterId" /></c> class. The <c><see cref="T:Android.Print.PrinterInfo" /></c> contains printer properties such as id, name, description, status,
and printer capabilities encapsulated in the <c><see cref="T:Android.Print.PrinterCapabilitiesInfo" /></c>
class. Printer capabilities describe how a printer can print content, for example what are
the supported media sizes, color modes, resolutions, etc.
</para><para tool="javadoc-to-mdoc" /></remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>
